Hello, everyone. Welcome to a discussion
of reputational stewardship, an
essential strategic pillar and
a focus of my own scholarship.
Here, you'll learn how to shape our
brand, manage reputational risks, and
help establish Vanderbilt as a global
thought leader in higher education.
This session invites you to consider
how every decision and interaction can
enhance our credibility and
elevate our standing in the world.
Your role as a leader is not just to
maintain a reputation, but to help
build it, ensuring that Vanderbilt's
values and achievements shine through.
Like all of us, you are
a guardian of a legacy.
Let's work together to enhance our
position as a beacon of excellence and
innovation.